question_data = [
        {"type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "medium",
         "category": "Entertainment: Books",
         "question": "Originally, the character Charlie from Charlie and the Chocolate Factory was going to be black.",
         "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
         },
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
         "question": "The Southeast Asian island of Borneo is politically divided among 3 countries.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt "
                     "on March 1st, 2010.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.",
         "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be "
                     "rabbits instead of squids.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
         "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Politics",
         "question": "The 2016 United States Presidential Election is the first time Hillary Clinton has run for "
                     "President.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
         "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                          "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also "
                                                      "interbred with the Denisovans.",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
